<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fons</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_all">All</string>
    <string name="title_trending">Trending</string>
    <string name="title_news">News</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="random">Welcome to Java—the world’s most widely used computer programming language. You’re
already familiar with the powerful tasks computers perform. Using this textbook, you’ll
write instructions commanding computers to perform those kinds of tasks. Software (i.e.,
the instructions you write) controls hardware (i.e., computers).
You’ll learn object-oriented programming—today’s key programming methodology.
You’ll create and work with many software objects in this text.
Java is the preferred language for meeting many organizations’ enterprise program-
ming needs. Java has also become the language of choice for implementing Internet-based
applications and software for devices that communicate over a network.
In use today are more than a billion general-purpose computers and billions more
Java-enabled cell phones, smartphones and handheld devices (such as tablet computers).
According to a study by eMarketer, the number of mobile Internet users will reach approx-
imately 134 million by 2013. 1 Other studies have projected smartphone sales to surpass
personal computer sales in 2011 2 and tablet sales to account for over 20% of all personal
computer sales by 2015. 3 By 2014, the smartphone applications market is expected to
exceed $40 billion, 4 which is creating significant opportunities for programming mobile
applications.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main3">Main3Activity</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
</resources>
